LAUREN BRENNAN

Security Policy Analysis

CONTACT

lbrenna@ncsu.edu +1 919 830 7081 www.cosmonaught.github.io LinkedIn: /laurenbbrennan

PROFILE

December 2017 graduate of North Carolina State University with a degree in Political Science - concentration in International Politics - and a focus on Information and Computer Security Policy. Experienced in social media, computer security fundamentals, policy analysis, and internal security assessments. Completed Associates in Science two weeks before high school graduation.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Risk Analyst Intern

Visa Inc. May 2017 - Aug 2017 Worked in both the Foster City, CA (USA) and London, UK offices to facilitate internal security assessments and develop content for executive board management and risk oversight committees.

Content Intern Demand Signals

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016

Assisted in writing both long and short form content for companies with a focus on Search Engine Optimization, troubleshot issues with HTML and CSS code within webpages, developed and deployed social media strategies.

Social IT Intern NC State University Sep 2015 - Jan 2017

Rebuilt the WISE Website, consulted on social media, set up social media accounts, implemented a social media plan for WISE. Helped troubleshoot issues with content and accessibility.

EXPERTISE

Policy Analysis **OSINT** Social Media Information Security Report Writing Copy Editing HTML/CSS

EDUCATION

2015 - 2017 Bachelor of Arts in Political Science North Carolina State University GPA: 3.59/3.36 **Associates in Science** 2013 - 2015 Durham Technical Community College GPA: 3.3

SKILLS

Leadership Communication Strategic Planning Visual Presentations **Public Speaking**

CERTIFICATIONS

- CompTIA Security+ Certified • Mobile Device Security Fundamentals Certified • PCI DSS Certified
- Web App Security Fundamentals Certified

LEADERSHIP

Treasurer - HackPack Security Member - IT Club @ PCOM Member - Women's Society of Cyberjutsu Founder -FemmeTEK